wpthemedetector.com 2017-09-07

# Privacy Policy - WordPress Theme Detector

To protect your privacy we provide this Privacy Policy document, which explains how we collect, use, and protect your personal information. Our Privacy Policy document is permanently accessible since it is linked at the bottom of our website pages, so that you can access it anytime you want. By visiting our website, you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

**PRIVACY POLICY AS PART OF OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE**  
Our privacy policy is part of, and subject to, our website’s terms and conditions of use.  
Our terms and conditions of use can be found on our website at [http://www.wpthemedetector.com/terms-and-conditions-of-use](http://www.wpthemedetector.com/terms-and-conditions-of-use/ "Terms and Conditions of Use")

**MODIFICATIONS OF THIS DOCUMENT**  
The contents of this document may be altered at any time due to any changes in our privacy policy or in our way to handle personal information that we may feel necessary to make. Should such changes be made, they will be effective immediately.  
If you are concerned about our current privacy policy, you should access this document and read it every time you enter our website before using it.  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, you can submit them to us by sending an e-mail to admin@wpthemedetector.com.

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**  
When visiting our website some basic information such as your IP address or the date and times of access will be automatically recorded, as it happens with most sites in the internet.  
We may also collect any information that you decide to provide us, for example by replying to the posts on our website or by sending us an e-mail message, but you can always choose not to provide us with information.

**USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
At the time being, our website does not send any kind of e-mail to users, thus contributing to avoid unwanted spam activities.  
Your e-mail address will be collected on the contact form included in our Contact page with the sole primary purpose of verifying that a real person is contacting us.  
Your e-mail address will not be used at all, except to individually reply to your e-mail message if you ask us to do so or if we consider that you will appreciate our reply to provide you with additional information about your query.  
The basic information automatically recorded when you access our website is only used to analyze trends and for statistical purposes. IP addresses are not related to any personal information.  
We will never give your data to third parties without your permission.

**LINKS TO EXTERNAL WEBSITES**  
For your convenience, our website includes links to other websites and shows information created by others. Please note that we shall under no circumstances be held responsible for their own privacy policies.  
Prior to using any website that you may access through the links provided in our website you may want to check and read its privacy policy, since it may not be in accordance with our own privacy policy.

**UPDATE INFORMATION**  
This document was last updated on October 10, 2012.
